keyplayr.com 2014-05-23

# KEYDOWNLOAD - Privacy Policy

KEYDOWNLOAD LTD.

Privacy Policy

KeyDownload is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy policy discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for our website and our service. By using our website or our service, you agree to be bound by the terms of this policy. 

**Personal Information**

Personal information is information that is unique to you (e-mail address). We may collect such personal information from you via our service. Because protecting your information is important to us, we do not sell any personal information to third parties. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

Our systems may automatically log certain non-personal information such as your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to help administer our service or to perform analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services. 

**Cookies**

Our services may involve the use of cookies to store information about your visits. In addition, during the course of providing advertisements to this site, third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer's hard drive. 

**Security**

We will take commercially reasonable measures in providing secure transmission of your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet from your personal computer to our servers and in securing such personal information stored on our systems. However, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet and that there is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of personal information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**External Links**

This site may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These sites have their own policies regarding privacy, which you should review before using them. We bear no responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for your convenience and information. 

**Use of Website by Children**

Our website is intended for the general audience and is not directed to children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 may not use our website. 

We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13.
